{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who is the love of your life?",
      "options": [
        "Rashidat",
        "Udale",
        "Anthonet",
        "Mamus",
        "Zara"
      ],
      "answer": "Anthonet"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which football club is the best in the world?",
      "options": [
        "Barcelona",
        "Bayern Munich",
        "Real Madrid",
        "Juventus",
        "Liverpool"
      ],
      "answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "How many major rivers do we have in Africa?",
      "options": [
        6,
        4,
        2,
        9,
        7
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the lingua franca of East Africa?",
      "options": [
        "Luo",
        "Zulu",
        "Shona",
        "Swahili",
        "Somali"
      ],
      "answer": "Swahili"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Where is Mount Kilimanjaro?",
      "options": [
        "Egypt",
        "Tanzania",
        "Uganda",
        "Rwanda",
        "Kenya"
      ],
      "answer": "Kenya"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which state is bordered by the most states in Nigeria?",
      "options": [
        "Ondo",
        "Imo",
        "Gombe",
        "Kogi",
        "Akwa-Ibom"
      ],
      "answer": "Kogi"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Yesterday, you ate 3 wraps of eba, today you ate six, how many will you eat tomorrow?",
      "options": [
        9,
        12,
        4,
        6,
        "Indeterminate"
      ],
      "answer": "Indeterminate"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which of the following is not a carnivore?",
      "options": [
        "Lion",
        "Crocodile",
        "Hippopotamus",
        "Tiger",
        "Cheetah"
      ],
      "answer": "Hippopotamus"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Mount Vesuvius is located in which country?",
      "options": [
        "Portugal",
        "Italy",
        "Spain",
        "France",
        "Brazil"
      ],
      "answer": "Italy"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The Isi-Agu cloth is native to which tribe in Africa?",
      "options": [
        "Maasai",
        "Akan",
        "Igala",
        "Igbo",
        "Fula"
      ],
      "answer": "Igbo"
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "options[]": [
        "1",
        "",
        "2",
        "",
        ""
      ],
      "answer": "e",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "2",
      "option2": "4",
      "option3": "3",
      "option4": "9",
      "option5": "r",
      "answer": "4",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "options[]": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "3",
        "9",
        "r"
      ],
      "answer": "4",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "23",
      "option2": "56",
      "option3": "34",
      "option4": "646",
      "option5": "3eq",
      "answer": "q3eq",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "options[]": [
        "23",
        "56",
        "34",
        "646",
        "3eq"
      ],
      "answer": "q3eq",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "23",
      "option2": "56",
      "option3": "34",
      "option4": "646",
      "option5": "3eq",
      "answer": "q3eq",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "options[]": [
        "23",
        "56",
        "34",
        "646",
        "3eq"
      ],
      "answer": "q3eq",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "QRQWREQ",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "3",
      "option3": "3",
      "option4": "3",
      "option5": "3",
      "answer": "2",
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "2",
      "option2": "2",
      "option3": "2",
      "option4": "2",
      "option5": "2",
      "answer": "2",
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "rer",
      "option3": "we",
      "option4": "weew",
      "option5": "weew",
      "answer": "weew",
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "rer",
      "option3": "we",
      "option4": "weew",
      "option5": "weew",
      "answer": "weew",
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "rer",
      "option3": "we",
      "option4": "weew",
      "option5": "weew",
      "answer": "weew",
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "2323",
      "option3": "232332",
      "option4": "23423",
      "option5": "2323",
      "answer": "23223",
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1900",
      "option2": "123",
      "option3": "2",
      "option4": "1952",
      "option5": "2332",
      "answer": "4",
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "question": "When did America gain her independence?",
      "option1": "1",
      "option2": "2",
      "option3": "1847",
      "option4": "1952",
      "option5": "12213",
      "answer": "1234",
      "id": 25
    }
  ],
  "users": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "email": "achilesolomon@gmail.com",
      "password": "shileth1818"
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "44555",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "email": "achile@gmail.com",
      "password": "shileth",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "email": "achile@gmail.com",
      "password": "shileth",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "email": "",
      "password": "",
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "email": "ewbgaiwhvh@",
      "password": "1234",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "1224",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "1224",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "1233",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "1233",
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345678",
      "id": 16
    },
    {
      "email": "hector91@gmail.com",
      "password": "12345",
      "id": 17
    },
    {
      "email": "meanini@gmail.com",
      "password": "123456",
      "id": 18
    },
    {
      "email": "",
      "password": "",
      "id": 19
    },
    {
      "email": "",
      "password": "",
      "id": 20
    }
  ],
  "routes": [
    {
      "url": [
        "login.html",
        "create_quiz.html",
        "signup.html",
        "results.html"
      ]
    }
  ]
}